Curriculum Vitae

Personal Information

Name Rupesh Sadashiv Ghumare

Date of Birth Nov 07th, 1991

Address At: Shivnai, Post: Ambedindori, Tal: Dindori, Dist: Nashik

Mobile 8275112705, 9673567974

Email rupeshghumare7@gmail.com



Presentation

I'm a Computer Science Engineer with specialization in Software Engineer graduated from Sanghavi College Of Engineering, Nashik (SCOE). I have 3 years of experience as Php back-end and Drupal, Wordpress Developer, I also have some basic experience in front-end development tools, and I have some experience in web Api development as well.

Education

2013–2017 **Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science,** Sanghavi College of Engineering, Nashik, Savitribai Phule University, Pune, (60.26% Aggregate)

2009–2013 Diploma in Computer Science, S.M.E.S. Polytechnic Nashik, MSBTE, Mumbai, (56%)

2008–2009 **H.S.C,** L.V.H College, Panchvati, Nashik, Savitribai Phule University, (52% Aggregate)

2006–2007 S.S.c, New English School, Ambedindori, Savitribai Phule University, (61.69% Aggregate)

Experience

2022–2023 **Php Developer,** vTech Solution Inc, Vadodara, Gujarat.

2021–2022 **Php Developer,** Valueit Technology, Nashik.

2019–2020 Php Developer, Webmatix Technology, Nashik.

2018–2019 Wordpress Developer, UMAVI Tecnologies, Nashik.

Industrial Project

Project Title voomcard

Technologies Front End – HTML,Bootstrap,Javascript, Back End – PHP Codeigniter, AJAX, MySQL.

Description This is admin panel website for Football club Members. admin can assign/unassign card to the members, also add club news. member can be used their app for see its cards etc.

Project Title kampdommer

Technologies Front End – HTML,Bootstrap,Javascript, Back End – PHP Codeigniter,AJAX, MySQL.

Description This is admin panel website for Football club. admin can add Refree,Refree Managers for football matches, admin also add team, match location so on. Refree,Refree Managers uses app for see their matches.

Project Title FCI Markets for share market

Technologies Front End - HTML, Bootstrap, Javascript, Back End - PHP Codeigniter, AJAX,

MySQL.

Description FCI Markets is a trading name of Foreign Currency Innovations Limited.

Academic Project

B.E

Project Title Reverse Calling and Location Detection Android Interface for Person Safety.

Technologies Front End – Android Interface, Back End – Java, MySQL.

Description This app is developed to get an emergency alert from the person in trouble to the parents

or relatives. Reverse calling is the prior feature of this app.

Diploma

Project Title Proxy Server.

Technologies Front End – c#, Back End – MySQL.

Description It was an project which was build to help my institute through which I can limit the use of

internet which was used by students. There was an additional feature which was to block

unauthorized web-sites.

Skills & Background Knowledge

Technical skills

Good skills in PHP (framework/s: Codeigniter and Basic knowledge Laravel)

Web Api Development

Web development (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Jquery, Javascript, Ajax, PHP) and CMS(Drupal9, Wordpress)

SQL and relational DBMS, and Mysql knowledge

OS admin skills in Linux and Windows

Personal skills

Enthusiastic and willing to take up challenges.

Ability to work as team member and relate to everyone in a multicultural environment.

Good in grasping and visualizing concepts.

Disciplined and hardworking.

Languages

Marathi Mothertongue

Hindi Intermidiate

English Intermidiate

Date: (Rupesh Sadashiv Ghumare)